[
  {
    "question": "In which part of your body would you find the cruciate ligament?",
    "answer": "Knee"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the main antagonist in the Shakespeare play Othello?",
    "answer": "Iago"
  },
  {
    "question": "What element is denoted by the chemical symbol Sn in the periodic table?",
    "answer": "Tin"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many of Henry VIII's wives were called Catherine?",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the most popular girls name in the UK in 2021?",
    "answer": "Olivia"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the 1976 film about the Watergate scandal, starring Robert Redford and Dustin Hoffman?",
    "answer": "All the President's Men"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which comedian was the second permanent host of Never Mind the Buzzcocks after Mark Lamarr?",
    "answer": "Simon Amstell"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which popular video game franchise has released games with the subtitles World At War and Black Ops?",
    "answer": "Call of Duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what US State is the city Nashville?",
    "answer": "Tennessee"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which rock band was founded by Fred Mercury in 1970?",
    "answer": "Queen"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the currency of Denmark?",
    "answer": "Krone"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Tennis Grand Slam is played on a clay surface?",
    "answer": "French Open"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which European country would you find the Rijksmuseum?",
    "answer": "Netherlands"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many films have Al Pacino and Robert De Niro appeared in together?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the old name for a Snickers bar before it changed in 1990?",
    "answer": "Marathon"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the head of state in Japan during the second world war?",
    "answer": "Emperor Hirohito"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
    "answer": "Mercury"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who wrote the novels Gone Girl and Sharp Objects?",
    "answer": "Gillian Flynn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which legendary surrealist artist is famous for painting melting clocks?",
    "answer": "Salvador Dali"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which football club plays its home games at Loftus Road?",
    "answer": "Queen Park Rangers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Continental United States has 4 time zones, can you name them?",
    "answer": "Pacific Mountain Central Eastern"
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the Turkish city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
    "answer": "Constantinople"
  },
  {
    "question": "From which US city do the band The Killers originate?",
    "answer": "Las Vegas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name the Coffee shop in US sitcom Friends.",
    "answer": "Central Perk"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many human players are there on each side in a polo match?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did Tony Blair become British Prime Minister?",
    "answer": "1997"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many times has England won the men's football World Cup?",
    "answer": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    "answer": "Wellington"
  },
  {
    "question": "Street artist Banksy is originally associated with which British city?",
    "answer": "Bristol"
  },
  {
    "question": "From what grain is the Japanese spirit Sake made?",
    "answer": "Rice"
  }
]